Guide to the Everett Education Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- United Teachers of Everett records, 1975-1992; 3849-006; .03 cubic feet (1 folder)
  - SALARY ISSUES, 1983-1992; SERIES I (Box-folder VF 2538 (1 Folder))
    - History of the Levy-Salary Issue materials (Memorandums, Package proposals and counterproposals, Correspondence), 1983-1992 (Box-folder VF 2538 (1 Folder))